This is the micro machine, man, presenting the most midget miniature motorcade of micro machine.
Each one has dramatic details,
terrific, turning precision paint jobs, plus incredible micromachine pocketplace.
That says a police station, fire station, restaurant, service station, and more.
Perfect pocket portables to take any place.
And there are many miniature places to play with, and each one comes with its own special edition,
micromachine vehicle,
and fun, fantastic features that miraculously move.
Raise the boat lift at the airport marina,
man the gun target at the army base, clean your car at the car wash, raise the toll bridge.
And these placets fit together to form a micro machine world.
Micro machine pocketplace that so tremendously tiny, so perfectly precise.
So dazzlingly detailed, you'll want to pocket them all.
Micromachines,
a micromachine pocket place, that's sold separately from Galube.
The smaller they are,
the better they are.